movements.tv 2018-11-08

# Privacy Policy - Movements

**Privacy Policy**

By using and visiting our website, you agree to the terms and conditions and Privacy policy of Movements. These terms and conditions apply to all users, and if you don't agree to these terms then please don't use the website. Movements has created this Privacy policy in order to demonstrate our determination to your online privacy. 

**What information do we collect:**

We collect information when you register to our website. You may be asked to enter your name, your email address, your country name, your address and your telephone number (if required) 

**What do we use your information for?**

We use your information just to enhance your experience and to improve our website. 

**Do we use Cookies?**

Yes we use cookies in order to: 

Count return visits to our site. Reporting anonymous statistical information on Web-site and advertisement usage. Enabling automatic logins. Personalize the website and to deliver content specific to your interests. Enable Google analyzer to monitor traffic to our website. 

**Do we use Third Party Links:**

No, we don't use third part links, unless they're our partners and we're bound to co-operate with each other. Parties other than our Partners are not allowed to share their links or promote there website without notifying us. 

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance:**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. 

**Information to outside parties/companies:**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it's release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety.   
However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

**Changes to our Privacy Policy:**

If we want to change our privacy policy, we'll post it here. 

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp. 

**Additional Choices for Residents in the European Economic Area:**

Individuals located in the European Economic Area, have certain statutory rights in relation to their Data. Subject to any exemptions provided by law, you may have the right to request access to your personal information, as well as to seek to update, delete, correct or transfer this information. You can usually do this using the settings provided in your Movements account. If you cannot use the settings, contact us by email at webmaster@movements.tv   
To the extent that Movements processing of your Data is subject to the General Data Protection Regulation (" **GDPR** "), and in addition to any consent you might have granted or contract you might have concluded with us, Movements relies on its legitimate interests, described above, to process your Data. 

**Web Beacons or Pixels:**

In addition to cookies, we may use other technologies such as web beacons or pixel tags, which can be embedded in web pages, videos, or emails. Web beacons or pixel tags are used to collect certain types of information from your browser or device; check whether you have viewed a particular web page, ad, or email message; and determine other usage details including: the time and date on which you viewed Content, the IP address of your computer, and the URL of the web page from which the Content was viewed. 

**Usage and Log Data:**

We collect information when you use the Movements Service or view Movements advertising outside of the Movements Service. We may also collect information from or about the computers, phones, tablets, or other devices where you install or access the Movements Service, depending on the permissions you've granted. Examples of this information may include your IP address, device ID number, browser and software characteristics (such as type and operating system or language settings), activity on the Movements Service including information about the videos you watch on the Movements Service (e.g. video titles and categories), the frequency and duration of your activities, page views, ad data, referral URLs, network state, and carrier information.
